Council on Foreign Relations Records: Studies Department Series, 1918-2004: Finding Aid
Princeton University Library. Department of Rare Books and Special Collections.
- Subseries 3B: Records of Groups, 1918-1996; 91.12 linear feet 219 boxes
  - Volumes, 1922-1973; 78 boxes
    - Western Policy Toward Eastern Europe, 1964; 1 folder (Box 175, Folder 4)
    - The OECD, 1964; 1 folder (Box 175, Folder 5)
    - Southern Africa, 1963-1964; 1 folder (Box 176, Folder 1)
    - German Foreign Policy and the American Interest, 1964-1965; 3 folders (Box 176, Folder 1 to 3)
    - Japan’s Role in the World, 1964-1965; 3 folders (Box 176, Folder 4 to 6)
    - South Africa, 1964-1965; 1 folder (Box 176, Folder 6)
    - South Africa continued, 1964-1965; 3 folders (Box 177, Folder 1 to 3)
    - The United States and China in World Affairs Part 1, 1962-1965; 3 folders (Box 177, Folder 4 to 6)
    - The United States and China in World Affairs Part 2, 1962-1965; 2 folders (Box 178, Folder 1 to 2)
    - The United States and China in World Affairs Part 3, 1962-1965; 4 folders (Box 178, Folder 3 to 6)
    - The United States and China in World Affairs Part 4, 1962-1965; 3 folders (Box 179, Folder 1 to 3)
    - The United States and China in World Affairs Part 5, 1962-1965; 4 folders (Box 179, Folder 4 to 7)
    - The United States and China in World Affairs Part 6, 1962-1965; 4 folders (Box 180, Folder 1 to 4)
    - The United States and China in World Affairs Part 7, 1962-1965; 3 folders (Box 180, Folder 5 to 7)
    - The International Flow of News, 1964-1965; 2 folders (Box 181, Folder 1 to 2)
    - The Newly Independent Nations of North Africa, 1964-1966; 3 folders (Box 181, Folder 2 to 4)
    - Critical World Problems and the United Nations, 1965-1966; 2 folders (Box 181, Folder 5 to 6)
    - Critical World Problems and the United Nations, 1965-1966; 1 folder (Box 182, Folder 1)
    - Political Leadership in Latin America, 1965-1966; 2 folders (Box 182, Folder 2 to 3)
    - Science and the National Interest, 1965-1966; 2 folders (Box 182, Folder 4 to 5)
    - Re-examination of American Foreign Policy, 1965-1966; 1 folder (Box 182, Folder 6)
    - Issues in United States Foreign Economic Policy, 1965-1966; 3 folders (Box 183, Folder 1 to 3)
    - Business and American Foreign Economic Policy, 1966; 1 folder (Box 183, Folder 3)
    - Atlantic Policy Studies Part 1, dates not examined; 2 folders (Box 183, Folder 4 to 5)
    - Atlantic Policy Studies Part 2, 1963-1966; 3 folders (Box 184, Folder 1 to 3)
    - Atlantic Policy Studies Part 3, 1963-1966; 3 folders (Box 184, Folder 4 to 6)
    - Atlantic Policy Studies Part 4, 1963-1966; 3 folders (Box 185, Folder 1 to 3)
    - Military Stability and Political Evolution in Europe, 1966-1967; 2 folders (Box 185, Folder 4 to 5)
    - Foreign Aid Policy, 1966-1967; 2 folders (Box 185, Folder 5 to 6)
    - South Asia as a New Focus of World Politics, 1966-1967; 1 folder (Box 186, Folder 1)
    - The Politics of Private Investment, 1966-1967; 1 folder (Box 186, Folder 2)
    - Vietnam’s Post-Conflict Prospects, 1967; 2 folders (Box 186, Folder 2 to 3)
    - The International Role of the Dollar, 1967-1968; 3 folders (Box 186, Folder 4 to 6)
    - The International Role of the Dollar, 1967-1968; 3 folders (Box 187, Folder 1 to 3)
    - Intelligence and Foreign Policy, 1967-1968; 3 folders (Box 187, Folder 4 to 6)
    - Trade Policy After the Kennedy Round, 1967-1968; 4 folders (Box 188, Folder 1 to 4)
    - American Policy Toward Africa, 1967-1968; 2 folders (Box 188, Folder 5 to 6)
    - United States Policy in the Caribbean, 1967-1968; 2 folders (Box 188, Folder 7 to 8)
    - African Issues, 1967-1968; 2 folders (Box 189, Folder 1 to 2)
    - The Middle East in the Aftermath of the Third Round, 1967-1968; 2 folders (Box 189, Folder 2 to 3)
    - Germany as a Focus for East-West Relations, 1967-1968; 2 folders (Box 189, Folder 4 to 5)
    - American Foreign Policy, 1967-1968; 1 folder (Box 189, Folder 5)
    - Ad Hoc Discussion on Arms Development, 1968; 1 folder (Box 190, Folder 1)
    - American Foreign Policy, 1967-1968; 1 folder (Box 190, Folder 2)
    - Ad Hoc Discussion on Vietnam, 1968; 3 folders (Box 190, Folder 3 to 5)
    - East-West Economic Relations, 1968-1969; 3 folders (Box 190, Folder 6 to 8)
    - Color in International Affairs, 1968-1969; 1 folder (Box 191, Folder 1)
    - Deployment and Control of Arms, 1968-1969; 2 folders (Box 191, Folder 2 to 3)
    - Japan’s Role in Asia, 1968-1969; 2 folders (Box 191, Folder 4 to 5)
    - Non-Nuclear Military Forces in a Nuclear Age, 1968-1969; 2 folders (Box 191, Folder 5 to 6)
    - Discussion Group on Latin America, 1968-1969; 2 folders (Box 192, Folder 1 to 2)
    - Multinational Enterprise in International Affairs, 1968-1969; 3 folders (Box 192, Folder 2 to 4)
    - The Media and American Foreign Policy, 1969-1970; 5 folders (Box 192, Folder 5 to 9)
    - United States Policy Toward East Asia, 1969-1970; 2 folders (Box 193, Folder 1 to 2)
    - Arms Control Issues, 1969-1970; 3 folders (Box 193, Folder 2 to 4)
    - American Aid Policy in the 70s, 1969-1970; 2 folders (Box 193, Folder 5 to 6)
    - United States Policy in the Middle East, 1969-1970; 1 folder (Box 193, Folder 7)
    - United States Policy in the Middle East, 1969-1970; 2 folders (Box 194, Folder 1 to 2)
    - New Forces in World Politics, 1969-1970; 2 folders (Box 194, Folder 3 to 4)
    - Japanese-American Relations, 1969-1970; 2 folders (Box 194, Folder 4 to 5)
    - Multilateral Economic Development Issues, 1969-1970; 2 folders (Box 195, Folder 1 to 2)
    - Foreign Affairs Organization for the Seventies, 1969-1970; 3 folders (Box 195, Folder 3 to 5)
    - International Financial Problems, 1969-1970; 1 folder (Box 195, Folder 6)
    - Atlantic Alliance in the 1970s, 1969-1970; 2 folders (Box 195, Folder 7 to 8)
    - The Changing Domestic Base of United States Foreign Policy, 1969-1970; 2 folders (Box 196, Folder 1 to 2)
    - The German Democratic Republic and Germany’s Future, 1970-1971; 3 folders (Box 196, Folder 3 to 5)
    - International Production, 1970-1971; 2 folders (Box 196, Folder 5 to 6)
    - United States Policy in Southeast and East Asia in the 1970s, 1970-1971; 3 folders (Box 197, Folder 1 to 3)
    - United States—Soviet Relations, 1969-1971; 3 folders (Box 197, Folder 4 to 6)
    - The Future Role of the Joint Chiefs of Staff, 1971; 2 folders (Box 197, Folder 6 to 7)
    - Relations Among the Industrialized Countries of the Non-Communist World, 1970-1971; 3 folders (Box 198, Folder 1 to 3)
    - The Political Role of Military Force, 1970-1972; 3 folders (Box 198, Folder 4 to 6)
    - Political Development, 1971-1972; 1 folder (Box 199, Folder 1)
    - Congress and National Security, 1972; 4 folders (Box 199, Folder 1 to 4)
    - International Order and International Institutions, 1971-1972; 4 folders (Box 199, Folder 5 to 8)
    - South Asia, 1971-1973; 2 folders (Box 200, Folder 1 to 2)
    - Japanese Foreign Policy, 1972-1973; 2 folders (Box 200, Folder 3 to 4)
    - The United States and Latin America, 1970-1972; 3 folders (Box 200, Folder 5 to 7)
    - Foreign Economic Policy, 1971-1972; 1 folder (Box 200, Folder 8)
    - International Aspects of National Policies for Science and Technology, 1971-1972; 3 folders (Box 201, Folder 1 to 3)
    - East Asia and the Great Powers, 1971-1972; 1 folder (Box 201, Folder 4)
    - American-Soviet Defense Expenditures, 1972; 3 folders (Box 201, Folder 5 to 7)
    - Law and Politics, 1971-1972; 4 folders (Box 202, Folder 1 to 4)
    - Soviet-American Relations, 1971-1973; 4 folders (Box 202, Folder 5 to 8)
    - Raw Materials and Foreign Policy, 1972-1973; 2 folders (Box 203, Folder 1 to 2)
    - African Development, 1972-1973; 2 folders (Box 203, Folder 2 to 3)
    - The Premises of America’s East Asia Policy: The Early 1950s, 1972-1973; 1 folder (Box 203, Folder 4)
    - SALT II, 1972-1973; 2 folders (Box 203, Folder 5 to 6)
    - Chinese Foreign Policy, 1972-1973; 3 folders (Box 204, Folder 1 to 3)
    - The American Interest in the Third World, 1972-1973; 3 folders (Box 205, Folder 1 to 3)
    - International Order/International Institutions, 1972-1973; 2 folders (Box 205, Folder 4 to 5)
  - Post-1973 Study Groups, 1959-2005; 93 boxes (1 partial)
    - Survey Discussion Group on U.S. Policy-Making Toward Latin America (First Meeting, 1973 June 4), 1973-1975, 4 folders (Box 206, Folder 1 to 4)
    - Current Issues Review Group on the Middle East (First Meeting, 1973 October 3), 1973-1974, 1 folder (Box 206, Folder 5)
    - Current Issues Review Group on Southern Africa (First Meeting, 1973 October 17), 1973-1974, 1 folder (Box 206, Folder 6)
    - Current Issues Review Group on Long Term Arms Control (First Meeting, 1973 October 31), 1973-1974, 1 folder (Box 207, Folder 1)
    - Current Issues Review Group on International Monetary Relations (First Meeting, 1973 November 7), 1973-1974, 1 folder (Box 207, Folder 2)
    - Current Issues Review Group on Japan (First Meeting, 1973 November 8), 1973-1974, 1 folder (Box 207, Folder 3)
    - Current Issues Review Group on European Security (First Meeting, 1973 November 14), 1973-1974, 1 folder (Box 207, Folder 4)
    - Current Issues Review Group on Trade (First Meeting, 1973 November 27), 1973-1974, 1 folder (Box 207, Folder 5)
    - Current Issues Review Group on Strategic Arms Limitation Talks II (First Meeting, 1973 December 5), 1973-1974, 1 folder (Box 207, Folder 6)
    - Current Issues Review Group on Southeast Asia (First Meeting, 1973 December 12), 1973-1974, 1 folder (Box 207, Folder 7)
    - Survey Discussion Group on International Terrorism (First Meeting, 1974 January 21), 1973-1974, 1 folder (Box 207, Folder 8)
    - Working Group on U.S.-European Relations (First Meeting, 1974 January 29), portions of 2 boxes
      - Atlantis Lost, 1975; 1 folder (Box 207, Folder 9)
      - Correspondence and Budget, 1973-1976; 1 folder (Box 207, Folder 10)
      - Meetings, 1973-1974; 1 folder (Box 208, Folder 1)
    - Current Issues Review Group on Inflation (First Meeting, 1974 February 5), 1973-1974, 1 folder (Box 208, Folder 2)
    - Current Issues Review Group on Northeast Asia (First Meeting, 1974 February 12), 1974, 1 folder (Box 208, Folder 3)
    - Meeting on Oil and the International Payments System, 1974 February 14; 1 folder (Box 208, Folder 4)
    - Survey Discussion Group on Soviet-American Relations (First Meeting, 1974 February 28), 1973-1974, 1 folder (Box 208, Folder 5)
    - Study Group on the Balkan-Mediterranean (First Meeting, 1974 April 16), 1974-1976, 1 folder (Box 208, Folder 6)
    - Population Discussion Meeting, 1974 April 17; 1 folder (Box 208, Folder 7)
    - Study Group on India's Development (First Meeting, 1974 April 23), 6 folders
      - Meeting One, 1974 April 23; 1 folder (Box 209, Folder 1)
      - Meeting Two, 1974 May 20; 1 folder (Box 209, Folder 2)
      - Meeting Three, 1974 September 23; 1 folder (Box 209, Folder 3)
      - Meeting Four, 1974 November 21, 1 folder (Box 209, Folder 4)
      - Meeting Five, 1975 January 28; 1 folder (Box 209, Folder 5)
      - Veit, Lawrence A., India: The Challenge of National Wealth, 1974-1975; 1 folder (Box 209, Folder 6)
    - Current Issues Review Group on Television and Public Policy (First Meeting, 1974 May 1), 1974, 1 folder (Box 209, Folder 7)
    - Current Issues Review Group on Domestic and Foreign Policy (First Meeting, 1974 May 23), 1974, 1 folder (Box 209, Folder 8)
    - Current Issues Review Group on Natural Resources and International Relations (First Meeting, ), 1974 May 30; 1973-1974; 1 folder (Box 210, Folder 1)
    - Current Issues Review Group on Ocean Policies (First Meeting, 1974 June 3), 1973-1975, 1 folder (Box 210, Folder 2)
    - Survey Discussion Group on Relations Among Communist States and Parties (First Meeting, 1974 October 7), 1974-1975, 2 folders (Box 210, Folder 3 to 4)
    - Survey Discussion Group on International Civil Aviation Policy (First Meeting, 1974 November 18), 1974-1975, 2 folders (Box 210, Folder 5 to 6)
    - Current Issues Review Group on Strategic Arms Control (First Meeting, 1974 December 12), 1974-1975, 1 folder (Box 210, Folder 7)
    - Current Issues Review Group on European-American Relations (First Meeting, 1975 January 8), 1974-1975, 1 folder (Box 210, Folder 8)
    - Survey Discussion Group on Two Koreas in East Asian Affairs (1975 January 8), 1974-1976; 3 folders (Box 211, Folder 1 to 3)
    - Conference on Nuclear Proliferation and World Order, 1975 January 11; 1 folder (Box 211, Folder 4)
    - Soviet-American Relations (First Meeting, 1975 January 15), 1974-1975, 2 folders (Box 211, Folder 5 to 6)
    - Current Issues Review Group on Southern Africa (First Meeting, 1975 January 16), 1974-1975, 1 folder (Box 211, Folder 7)
    - Current Issues Review Group on Middle East (First Meeting, 1975 February 4), 1974-1975, 1 folder (Box 211, Folder 8)
    - Survey Discussion Group on International Aspects of Brazil's Development (First Meeting, 1975 February 4), portions of 2 boxes
      - 1975, 2 folders (Box 211, Folder 9 to 10)
      - 1975-1976, 2 folders (Box 212, Folder 1 to 2)
    - Current Issues Review Group on Southeast Asia (First Meeting, 1975 February 6), 1974-1975, 1 folder (Box 212, Folder 3)
    - Survey Discussion Group on OPEC (First Meeting, 1975 February 26), 1974-1976, 3 folders (Box 212, Folder 4 to 6)
    - Conference on Japan's Economic Prospects and Their Political Implications, 1975 March 1; 1 folder (Box 212, Folder 7)
    - Current Issues Review Group on Cuba (First Meeting, 1975 March 13), 1974-1975, 1 folder (Box 212, Folder 8)
    - Current Issues Review Group on Cuba (First Meeting, 1975 March 13), 1974-1975, 1 folder (Box 213, Folder 1)
    - Survey Discussion Group on National Security in a Constitutional Framework (First Meeting, 1975 April 8), 1975-1976, 2 folders (Box 213, Folder 2 to 3)
    - Foreign Investments in the U.S. (First Meeting, 1975 May 12), 1975-1976, 2 folders (Box 213, Folder 4 to 5)
    - Current Issues Review Group on Panama-U.S. Relations (First Meeting, 1975 September 24), 1975-1976, 1 folder (Box 213, Folder 6)
    - Current Issues Review Group on Strategic Arms Control (First Meeting, 1975 October 15), 1975-1979, 1 folder (Box 213, Folder 7)
    - Survey Discussion Group on Foreign Policy Organization (First Meeting, 1975 October 29), 1975-1976, 4 folders (Box 214, Folder 1 to 4)
    - Current Issues Review Group on Domestic Politics in Western Europe (First Meeting, 1975 October 30), 1975-1976, 1 folder (Box 214, Folder 5)
    - Current Issues Review Group on Middle East (First Meeting, 1975 November 3), 1975-1976, 1 folder (Box 214, Folder 6)
    - Survey Discussion Group on Venezuela's Changing International Role (First Meeting, 1975 November 20), more than 3 folders
      - Author's Workshop, 1976 September 30-October 1; 1 folder (Box 214, Folder 7)
      - Correspondence Regarding Papers, 1975-1976; 1 folder (Box 214, Folder 8)
      - Meetings, 1975-1976; 2 folders (Box 214, Folder 9 to 10)
    - Current Issues Review Group on Southeast Asia (First Meeting, 1975 December 1), 1975-1977, 1 folder (Box 215, Folder 1)
    - Current Issues Review Group on International Finance (First Meeting, 1976 January 5), 1975-1976, 1 folder (Box 215, Folder 2)
    - Survey Discussion Group on Sino-American Relations (First Meeting, 1976 January 12), more than 2 folders
      - Meetings, 1976; 2 folders (Box 215, Folder 3 to 4)
      - Planning, 1975-1976; 1 folder (Box 215, Folder 5)
    - Current Issues Review Group on the Horn of Africa (First Meeting, 1976 January 20), 1975-1976, 1 folder (Box 215, Folder 6)
    - Transnational Enterprises and the Future of International Relations (First Meeting, 1976 January 22), portions of 2 boxes
      - Correspondence, 1975; 1 folder (Box 215, Folder 7)
      - Correspondence, 1976; 1 folder (Box 216, Folder 1)
      - Correspondence, 1977-1978; 1 folder (Box 216, Folder 2)
      - Meetings, 1975-1977; 4 folders (Box 216, Folder 3 to 6)
    - Survey Discussion Group on Arms Trade and Foreign Policy (First Meeting, 1976 February 3), more than 2 folders
      - Meetings, 1976-1977; 3 folders (Box 216, Folder 7 to 9)
      - Planning, 1975-1976; 1 folder (Box 216, Folder 10)
    - Meeting on International Commodity Buffer Stocks, 1976 March 20; 1 folder (Box 217, Folder 1)
    - Role of Cuba in Southern Africa (First Meeting, 1976 May 6), 1976, 1 folder (Box 217, Folder 2)
    - Current Issues Review Group on the International Transfer of Technology (First Meeting, 1976 September 16), 1976-1977, 2 folders (Box 217, Folder 3 to 4)
    - Working Group on the Middle East (First Meeting, 1976 November 9), 1976-1977, 1 folder (Box 217, Folder 5)
    - Current Issues Review Group on Journalists and Editors on Latin America and Inter-American Affairs (First Meeting, 1976 November 11), 1976-1977, 1 folder (Box 217, Folder 6)
    - Current Issues Review Group on Current Developments in China (First Meeting, 1976 November 22), 1976-1977, 1 folder (Box 217, Folder 7)
    - Current Issues Review Group on Nigeria (First Meting, 1976 December 2), 1976-1977, 1 folder (Box 218, Folder 1)
    - Current Issues Review Group on Nuclear Proliferation (First Meeting, 1976 December 2), 1976-1977, 1 folder (Box 218, Folder 2)
    - Survey Discussion Group on Congressional-Executive Relations in Foreign Policy (First Meeting, 1976 December 9), 1976-1977, 2 folders (Box 218, Folder 3 to 4)
    - Survey Discussion Group on Future of the U.S. Navy (First Meeting, 1977 January 12), more than 2 folders
      - Meetings, 1976-1978; 4 folders (Box 218, Folder 5 to 8)
      - Planning, 1976-1978; 1 folder (Box 218, Folder 9)
    - Survey Discussion Group on Co-operative Diplomacy and U.S. Foreign Policy (First Meeting, 1977 January 18), 1976-1977, 2 folders (Box 219, Folder 1 to 2)
    - U.S. Policy Toward Africa (First Meeting, 1977 January 26), more than 2 folders
      - Meetings, 1976-1977; 3 folders (Box 219, Folder 3 to 5)
      - Planning, 1976-1977; 1 folder (Box 219, Folder 6)
    - Survey Discussion Group on Intelligence Activities (First Meeting, 1977 January 27), 1976-1977, 2 folders (Box 219, Folder 7 to 8)
    - Survey Discussion Group on Human Rights and U.S. Policy (First Meeting, 1977 January 31), more than 2 folders
      - Meetings, 1976-1977; 3 folders (Box 220, Folder 1 to 3)
      - Planning, 1976-1977; 1 folder (Box 220, Folder 4)
    - Conference on the Current Situation and Outlook in Japan (Conference Date, 1977 February 12), 1976-1977, 1 folder (Box 220, Folder 5)
    - Current Issues Review Group on U.S.-Mexican Relations (First Meeting, 1977 February 22), 1976-1977, 1 folder (Box 220, Folder 6)
    - Working Group on the Belgrade Conference (First Meeting, 1977 March 7), 1976-1977, 2 folders (Box 220, Folder 7 to 8)
    - Current Issues Review Group on the International Debt Structure (First Meeting, 1977 March 23), 1976-1977, 1 folder (Box 221, Folder 1)
    - Ocean Policies Review Group (First Meeting, 1977 May 31), 1975-1977, 1 folder (Box 221, Folder 2)
    - Study Group on America's Impact on the World (First Meeting, 1977 October 20), 1975-1978, 2 folders (Box 221, Folder 3 to 4)
    - Discussion Group on Canada (First Meeting, 1977 November 10), 1977-1979, 1 folder (Box 221, Folder 5)
    - Discussion Group on International Cooperation in Meeting Basic Human Needs (First Meeting, 1977 November 25), 1977-1978, 1 folder (Box 221, Folder 6)
    - Study Group on Japan (First Meeting, 1977 November 30), 1977-1978, 2 folders (Box 222, Folder 1 to 2)
    - Discussion Group on India (First Meeting, 1977 December 8), 1977-1978, 1 folder (Box 222, Folder 3)
    - Discussion Group on NATO Defense Strategy (First Meeting, 1977 December 12), 1977-1978, 1 folder (Box 222, Folder 4)
    - Study Group on the Changing Structure of the International Raw Materials Industry (First Meeting, 1977 December 19), 1977-1979, 2 folders (Box 222, Folder 5 to 6)
    - Discussion Group on Oil and the Problems of the Persian Gulf (First Meeting, 1978 January 25), 1977-1978, 1 folder (Box 222, Folder 7)
    - Discussion Group on Western Europe (First Meeting, 1978 February 8), 1977-1979, 1 folder (Box 223, Folder 1)
    - Ocean Policies Review Group (First Meeting, 1978 February 16), 1977-1982, 1 folder (Box 223, Folder 2)
    - Study Group on Immigration and U.S. Foreign Policy (First Meeting, 1978 March 20), 1977-1978, 2 folders (Box 223, Folder 3 to 4)
    - Study Group on Soviet and American Concepts of Détente (First Meeting, 1978 March 23), 1976-1978, 2 folders (Box 223, Folder 5 to 6)
    - Discussion Group on Central America (First Meeting, 1978 April 5), 1977-1978, 1 folder (Box 223, Folder 7)
    - Seminar on the U.S.S.R and the Sources of Soviet Policy (First Meeting, 1978 April 14), more than 3 folders
      - Correspondence, 1978-1979; 1 folder (Box 224, Folder 1)
      - Planning, 1977-1978; 1 folder (Box 224, Folder 2)
      - Sessions, 1978; 3 folders (Box 224, Folder 3 to 5)
    - Joint Discussion Group on Executive-Congressional Relations, with Carnegie Endowment for International Peace (First Meeting, 1978 April 27), 1977-1978, 1 folder (Box 224, Folder 6)
    - Discussion Group on South Africa and the Western Alliance (First Meeting, 1978 May 16), 1977-1978, 1 folder (Box 224, Folder 7)
    - Discussion Group on U.S. Food and Agriculture Policy (First Meeting, 1978 October 11), 1978-1979, portions of 2 boxes
      - Meetings, 1978-1979; 2 folders (Box 224, Folder 8 to 9)
      - Planning, 1977-1979; 1 folder (Box 225, Folder 1)
    - Study Group on the Soviet Union and World Economy (First Meeting, 1978 October 26), 4 folders
      - Background Papers, 1978-1979; 1 folder (Box 225, Folder 2)
      - Meetings, 1978-1979; 1 folder (Box 225, Folder 3)
      - Planning, 1978-1980; 1 folder (Box 225, Folder 4)
      - Publication, 1979; 1 folder (Box 225, Folder 5)
    - Soviet Policy in Asia (First Meeting, 1978 November 3), more than 3 folders
      - Correspondence, 1979-1980; 1 folder (Box 225, Folder 6)
      - Correspondence, 1981-1983; 1 folder (Box 225, Folder 7)
      - Meetings, 1977-1979; 2 folders (Box 225, Folder 8 to 9)
    - Study Group on the Soviet Union and the Problem of Regional Instability (First Meeting, 1978 November 8), 1978-1979, 2 folders (Box 226, Folder 1 to 2)
    - Discussion Group on International Finance and Latin American Development (First Meeting, 1978 November 8), 1978-1979, 2 folders (Box 226, Folder 3 to 4)
    - Discussion Group on Congress and Foreign Policy, with Carnegie Endowment for International Peace (First Meeting, 1978 November 13), 1978-1979, 2 folders (Box 226, Folder 5 to 6)
    - Discussion Group on the Soviet Union in Africa (First Meeting, 1978 December 14), 1978-1979, 2 folders (Box 227, Folder 1 to 2)
    - Study Group on the Interaction of Jewish and Palestinian Nationalism (First Meeting, 1979 January 8), 1978-1979, 1 folder (Box 227, Folder 3)
    - Parallax: Conflicting Perceptions in Soviet-American Relations, 1959-1979 (First Meeting, 1979 January 15), 1978-1979, 3 folders (Box 227, Folder 4 to 6)
    - Discussion Group on Contemporary U.S. Policy Toward the Soviet Union (First Meeting, 1979 January 17), 1978-1979, 1 folder (Box 227, Folder 7)
    - Discussion Group on the Arab-Israeli Conflict (First Meeting, 1979 January 22), 1978-1979, 1 folder (Box 228, Folder 1)
    - Discussion Group on Trade and Industrial Policy (First Meeting, 1979 February 7), 1978-1979, 1 folder (Box 228, Folder 2)
    - Study Group on Conflict and Crisis Resolution in Africa (First Meeting, 1979 March 8), 1978-1979, 2 folders (Box 228, Folder 3 to 4)
    - Study Group on Oil Factor in U.S. Foreign Policy (First Meeting, 1979 September 17), 1979-1980, 3 folders (Box 228, Folder 5 to 7)